sportsbettingdime.com 2017-01-28

# Privacy Policy| Top 10 Sports Betting Sites

**PRIVACY POLICY**

**sportsbettingdime.com**

This privacy policy (the “ **Policy** ”) governs your (“ **You/Your** “) use of the website **sportsbettingdime.com** (the “ **Site** “). It further sets out how the we, the proprietors of the Site, (“ **We/Us/Our** “) will handle Your personally identifiable information.

The Policy is incorporated into the Terms and forms part of the Terms, but shall not derogate in any way from the Terms. All capitalized words and phrases used in the Policy that are not defined in the Policy shall have the same meaning as they do in the Terms.

In visiting or using the Site, You consent to Our collection, use, and disclosure of Your Personal Information (as that term is defined in Section 2) as set out herein.

  1. **Information Collection and Use**

We may log Personal Information (as defined in Section 2) when You visit the site, including IP address, pages viewed, time of access, date of access, Your search and Site navigation preferences, and clicking habits.

We may also track certain aggregate information that cannot be personally traced to any individual (“ **Aggregate Information** ”), such as the number of Site visitors, the number of visitors to each page, and the browser used by the visitors. We may analyze this data for trends and statistics, but such information will only be used and disclosed in aggregate form; it will not contain any Personal Information.

We may use Personal Information and Aggregate Information to improve visitors’ experience on the Site. We may also analyze Personal Information and Aggregate Information to learn more about how visitors access the site, and customize advertisements and other content thereto. We may also use Personal Information and Aggregate Information to test changes to the Site and make improvements to Site functionality.

  2. **Privacy Legislation**

We comply with all applicable privacy legislation regulating the retention, use and disclosure of Personal Information by private sector organizations (the “ **Privacy Legislation** ”).

We will only collect, use or disclose Personal Information in accordance with Legislation and this Policy.

“ **Personal Information** ” means information about an identifiable individual, including their name, home address, telephone number, social insurance number, financial information (including but not limited to credit card information), and gender. Personal information _does not_ include information that would allow an individual to be contacted at a place of business; examples include a person’s

  * position or title,
  * business telephone number
  * business address.

We have appointed a privacy officer (“ **Privacy Officer** ”) as per the requirements of the Privacy Legislation. Our Privacy Officer is responsible for compliance with this Policy and the Privacy Legislation. The Privacy Officer can be contacted by e-mail: privacy.officer@sportsbettingdime.com

  3. **Disclosure of Personal Information to Third-Parties**

We will not disclose or share Personal Information with third-parties except as set out in this Policy. We may provide Personal Information and Aggregate Information, including the number of visitors to the Site and time of access to the Site, to certain third-parties, such as vendors, service agencies, and advertisers, whom we engage to assist Us in providing Our Services to You.

We reserve the right to disclose Your Personal Information and communications on the Site when required by law.

In the event of a merger or other corporate reorganization, We may transfer your Personal Information to Our successor or purchaser.

  4. **Age of Majority**

This Site is only intended for individuals over the age of 17 _and_ over the age of majority in their jurisdiction. The materials on the Site and the Services are _not_ targeted at individuals under the age of 18. By using the Site, You warrant that You are above the age of 17 _and_ the age of majority in Your jurisdiction. If You are not, You agree to stop using the Site immediately.

  5. **Cookies and Widgets**

We may use cookies (pieces of data stored on Your hard-drive which contain information about Your access to the Site) to improve visitors’ overall Site experience. Cookies generally do not permit identification of Your Personal Information. However, it may be possible for You to disable the Our use of cookies through Your internet browser settings.

The Site may also employ widgets (software aimed at collecting information regarding Your browsing habits) in order to provide You access to Site content. Widgets embedded on the Site may collect information provided by visitors which is then disclosed to third-parties.

Our advertisers may place such widgets in Your internet browser or use web beacons to collect information about the user. Such third-parties may collect and commercially exploit any information provided by users, subject to applicable laws and regulations. The use of such information is not covered by this Policy as we do not have direct control over how the information collected by these third-parties is used.

  6. **Links to Third Party Websites**

We provide links to other websites and resources over which We do not have control (“ **External Sites** “). Said links are not an endorsement of External Sites. You agree that We are not responsible for the content of such External Sites. Your use of External Sites is subject to their terms of use and privacy policies.

By linking from the Site to External Sites, We may share some information with the External Sites. This information is generally not personally identifiable information but may include information about Your use of the Site, including the location from where You accessed the Site, which link You used to navigate to the External Site, and the date and time that You navigated to the External Site.

  7. **Broadcast Email Providers**

We may employ third party marketing providers (“ **Broadcast Email Providers** ”) to assist Us in contacting Our visitors by providing broadcast email services for Us. If You provide Us with Your email address and opt in to receive emails from Us, We may share your name and email address as necessary for such Broadcast Email Providers to provide that service. Such Broadcast Email Providers are prohibited from using Your Personal Information for promotional purposes. Any emails You received from Us or on Our behalf shall have an opt-out or unsubscribe option clearly displayed allowing You to opt-out or unsubscribe from future emails or adjust email subscription settings from Us.

  8. **Referrals**

We do not trade, sell or otherwise share your Personal Information with third-parties, but the Site may earn revenue by way of referral fees ( _i.e._ fees earned by Us when visitors from the Site click out to an External Site).

  9. **Security**

We are committed to ensuring Your Personal Information is protected. We may employ security measures (including internal procedures and software and hardware solutions) designed to help protect Your Personal Information from loss, unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration or destruction. To protect Your Personal Information, we will use industry-standard security measures, including Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

The evolving nature of Our business may require Us to situate Our computer systems outside of North America or the European Union. Personal Information stored in such other jurisdictions may be subject to disparate privacy legislation. By using the Site, You consent to the transfer of Your Personal Information to such other jurisdictions . You further acknowledge that this may affect the level of protection Your Personal Information receives.

  10. **Updates**

From time to time, We may amend this Policy. Before any such amendments are effective, We will provide notice of the amendments prominently on the Site for a minimum of thirty (30) days. By continuing to use the Site and/or Services after such amendments are effective, You agree to abide by the amended Policy. If You do not agree to be bound by the amended Policy, You must cease using the Site immediately.

—

**Effective Date:** February 4, 2016
